Fuad Nasser-Aldeen

Personal Info



+972-50-395-5900



<u>fuad.nasseraldeen@gmail.com</u>



<u>linkedin.com/in/fuad-nasseraldeen</u>



github.com/fuad-nasseraldeen



www.fuad-nasseraldeen.com

OBJECTIVE

Software Engineer that keen to play a key role from planning up to delivering a solution in the digital world and to elevate of user experience to the next level and interested in a full-time position in software development.

Technological Skills

• React • Java • Node.js

Redux • Hooks • Express.js

- CSS/SCSS SQL HTML
- Javascript (ES5,ES6)/Typescript

Hackathon

Amdocs 2022 – **Development teams Hackathon**, **1**st place in 6-developer team among 60 teams (more than 100 participants), 24 hour intense of hard #teamwork for designing and implementing drag drop component to improve the user experience for our website.

Skills

- Good at teamwork and Cooperation.
- Well organized. Fast self-learner.
- Responsible.
- Time management
- Capable with meeting deadlines, and work under pressure

Languages

Arabic (Native) Hebrew (Bilingual) English (Advanced)

Experience

Software Engineer at Amdocs, Nazareth/Raanana

03/2021 - 01/2023

- planning and implementing user interfaces using REACTJS. For an account in the Philippines, my role was working in UI as well as joining Business Analysis meetings and Backend planning to deliver most efficient and effective solution.
- Work closely, with customer representatives, to improve the system UX and provide better usability and user experience for both of their agents and end users.
- Developed and maintained new features in modular highly customizable React & Redux based projects
- Identified and fixed bugs/defects in Development/Staging/Production environments, including compiled ES5 code
- Worked in Agile development teams alongside foreign coworkers and assisted new developers with their tasks
- Used enterprise-grade programs/tools such as Teams, Jira, Perforce, Jenkins, Swagger, SonarQube, GitHub

Java Full Stack Development bootcamp Amdocs & Co-impact

09/2020 - 01/2021

- RACTJS, Java Core, Advanced Java, Extreme Java, Java 8, Restful API, Spring, Spring Core, Spring Boot, Spring MVC, CSS, HTML, JS, Dockers, K8, Oracle MySQL.
- High emphasis on clean, elegant, maintainable, readable, and efficient code.

Projects

Social network for developers

11/2022 - 012/2022

- A MERN stack application Developed using REACT and node.js with mongoDB and Heroku Cloud
- It is a small social network app that includes authentication, profiles and forum posts, like/dislike a post and comment on a post.
- Please feel free to take a look -> https://social-network-fuad.herokuapp.com/

Coupon System Project

12/2020 - 02/2021

- Developed an application using **Java SpringBoot and Angular**.
- End to End application that allow us to handle and create query with DB.
- It acts as a Micro Service that shows an implementation which allows companies To CRUD coupons for their customers.
- the Customers can purchase and use those Coupons, and get a discount in that company's "business". (See <u>Demo</u>)

Education

2013-2018

- Jerusalem College of Engineering (JCE) | Jerusalem
- B.Sc. Software Engineering

2014-2016

• Private **tutor** for several courses such as Introduction to Programming in Java, Data Structures, Algorithms, and Probability & Statistics (for college students).

References and letters of recommendation available upon request.